Last updated: March 3, 2025

Limitless AI, Inc. (**“Rewind”, “Limitless”, “we”, “us”, “our”**) is committed to protecting your personal information and your right to privacy. Your trust & privacy is more important to us than anything else. And that is why **we will never sell your data or use your data for advertising.**If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy notice (“Privacy Policy”) or our practices with regard to your personal information, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.limitless.ai/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). When you visit our websites, including https://rewind.ai; https://limitless.ai and any of our associated websites (collectively, the **Website**), use our applications, as the case may be (the **App**), use our wearable device (the **Pendant**), and more generally, use any of our services that link to this Privacy Policy (the **“Services,”** which include the Website, App, and Pendant), we appreciate that you are trusting us with your personal information. We take your privacy very seriously. In this Privacy Policy, we seek to Privacy Policy, we seek to explain to you in the clearest way possible what information we collect, how we use it, and what rights you have in relation to it. We hope you take some time to read through it carefully, as it is important. If there are any terms in this Privacy Policy that you do not agree with, please discontinue the use of our Services immediately. If you are located in the European Economic Area (**“EEA”**) or the United Kingdom (**“UK”**), “personal information” means any information relating to an identified or identifiable individual. This Privacy Policy applies to all information collected from you through our Services (which, as described above, includes our Website, App, and Pendant), as well as our Services (which, as described above, includes our Website, App, and Pendant), as well as any related services, sales, marketing, or events conducted by or for us. Beyond the Privacy Policy, your use of our Services is also subject to our Terms of Service. References in this Privacy Policy to “you” and “your” refer to each user and customer of our Services and each visitor to our Website.

Information We Collect
----------------------

### A. Information You Provide to Us.

You provide us with personal information about yourself when you use, register or sign up for our App, Pendant, Website or other Services, and when you communicate with us, make a payment to us or in connection with the Services, or subscribe to our newsletter or updates. Such personal information may include for example your name, e-mail address, physical address, phone number and other contact information.

Communications.

If you contact us directly, we may receive additional information about you. For example, when you contact our Customer Support Team, we will receive your name, email address, the contents of a message or attachments that you may send to us, and other information you choose to provide. When we send you emails, we may use embedded pixels or other technologies to track information about your receipt and interaction with our emails, such as whether and when you open them, whether you access any links included in our emails, how long you read our emails, whether you forward our emails and to whom, your Location Information (described below), and your Device Information (described below), to learn how to deliver a better customer experience and improve our Services.

Careers.

If you decide that you wish to apply for a job with us, you may submit your contact information and resume online. We will collect the information you choose to provide on your resume, such as your education and employment experience. You may also apply through Lever or other third-party applications or services. If you do so, we will collect the information you make available to us on Lever or such third-party applications or services or on any external job posting in which you found us.

Payment Information.

If you make a purchase through our Services, your payment-related information, such as credit card or other financial information, is collected by our third-party payment processor on our behalf.

Services Information.

When you use our Services, we may receive any personal information you provide or otherwise make available to us via our Services. For example, when you use Limitless’ manual or automatic transcription and summarization features, we may receive audio and text-based transcriptions derived from the audio capture of your meetings or non-meeting audio recordings (e.g., voice memos). We may receive additional information related to audio and video recordings on your device or computer, such as meeting and calendar details.

Information Generated by or Collected From Third-Party Services.

As part of our Services’ integration or interfacing with third-party services or technologies, such as OpenAI and other artificial intelligence services, we may also collect the outputs and other data generated by or received from such third-party services or technologies, such as the audio transcription summaries of your audio recordings and any other data generated by the third-party integrations and interfaces.

### B. Information We Collect When You Use Our Website.

When you use our Website, we automatically collect personal information about your device and how you use our Website.

Location Information.

When you use our Website, we infer your general location information, for example, by using your internet protocol (IP) address.

‍Device Information.

We receive information about the device and software you use to access our Website, including IP address, web browser type, operating system version, manufacturer, application installations, and device identifiers.

Usage Data.

We collect log and usage data relating to your use of the Website and Services, including information about your use of the features and functionality therein. We also collect analytics and crash reporting that includes emails, IPs, and device info.

‍Information from Cookies and Similar Technologies.

We and our third-party partners collect information using cookies, pixel tags, or similar technologies. Our third-party partners, such as analytics partners, may use these technologies to collect information about your online activities over time and across different services. Cookies are small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters. We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie disappears after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to our Website.

We use cookies, beacons, invisible tags, and similar technologies (collectively “Cookies”) to collect information about your browsing activities and use of our Services to distinguish you from other users of our Services. This aids your experience when you use our Services and allows us to improve the functionality of our Services. Cookies can be used for performance management (i.e., collecting information on how our Services are being used for analytics purposes). They can also be used for functionality management, enabling us to make your visit more efficient by, for example, remembering language preferences, passwords, and log-in details. Below is an overview of the types of Cookies we and third parties may use to collect personal information.

Strictly Necessary Cookies.

Some Cookies are strictly necessary to make our Services available to you. We cannot provide you with our Services without this type of Cookies.

Functional Cookies.

Functional Cookies are used to recognize you when you return to our Services. This enables us to adapt our content for you and remember your preferences. For example, we use functional Cookies to remember your choice of language or region.

Analytical or Performance Cookies.

We also use Cookies for website analytics purposes in order to operate, maintain and improve our Services.

Please review your web browser’s “Help” file to learn the proper way to modify your cookie settings. Please note that if you delete or choose not to accept cookies from the Service, you may not be able to utilize the features or functionality of the Services to their fullest potential.

### C. Information We Collect When You Use Our App or Pendant.

Our Services collect information from certain third-party applications that interface with or connect to our App and Pendant, such as Gmail and Google Calendar. For example, we may collect meeting events and information from your Google Calendar entries and/or meeting information from your emails in Gmail which we may use for providing meeting preparation information as part of the Services. You can also record and transcribe meetings in connection with our Services, and in such case we would collect information and content relating to such recordings and transcriptions.

Our App and Pendant utilize product analytics and crash reporting tools. The information we collect from our App and Pendant includes:

Log and Usage Data.

Log and usage data is service-related, diagnostic, usage, and performance information our servers automatically collect when you access or use our App or Pendant and which we record in log files or other data usage files. Depending on how you interact with us, this log data and usage data may include your IP address, device information, and settings and information about your activity in the App or Pendant (such as the date/time stamps associated with your usage and other actions you take such as which features you use), device event information (such as system activity, error reports – sometimes called \`crash dumps\` -- and hardware settings).

App Device Data.

We collect device data such as information about your device or computer you use to access the App. Depending on the device or computer used, this device data may include information such as your IP address (or proxy server), device and application identification numbers, location, hardware model, Internet service provider and/or mobile carrier, operating system, and system configuration information.

Audio Recordings.

The App collects all spoken audio from the Pendant whenever the Pendant is turned on.

Vendors and Service Providers.

We may disclose any information we receive to vendors and service providers retained in connection with the provision of our Services. For example, we use cloud service providers to securely store your audio recordings, and the transcriptions of your audio recordings are sent to third-party services, such as Google Gemini or OpenAI, to provide you with summaries of your audio recordings. Data sent to third-party AI providers for transcription and summarization is not used for training and is deleted after 30 days.

How We Use the Information We Collect
-------------------------------------

We use information from or about you for a variety of purposes detailed below. These purposes include providing and improving our Services, communicating with you, marketing to you, preventing fraud, enforcing our Terms of Service, complying with legal requirements, and other purposes we tell you about when we collect your information.

We use the information we collect:

*   To provide, maintain, improve, test and enhance our Services and to develop new products and services;
*   To train, develop, and improve the artificial intelligence, machine learning, and models that we use to support our Services;
*   To personalize your experience with our Services such as by providing tailored content and recommendations;
*   To understand and analyze how you use our Services and develop new products, services, features, and functionality;
*   To communicate with you, provide you with updates and other information relating to our Services, provide information that you request, respond to comments and questions, and otherwise provide customer support;
*   To generate anonymized, aggregate data containing only de-identified, non-personal information that we may use for any legal purpose;
*   To facilitate transactions and payments;
*   To find and prevent fraud and respond to trust and safety issues that may arise;
*   For compliance purposes, including enforcing our Terms of Service or other legal rights, or as may be required by applicable laws and regulations or requested by any judicial process or governmental agency; and
*   For other purposes for which we provide specific notice at the time the information is collected.

Legal Bases For Processing European Information
-----------------------------------------------

If you are located in the European Economic Area or the United Kingdom, we only process your personal information when we have a valid “legal basis,” including as set forth below.

Consent.

‍We may process your personal information where you have consented to certain processing of your personal information.

Contractual Necessity.

We may process your personal information where required to provide you with our Services. For example, we may need to process your personal information to respond to your inquiries or requests.

Compliance with a Legal Obligation.

We may process your personal information where we have a legal obligation to do so. For example, we may process your personal information to comply with tax, labor, and accounting obligations.

Legitimate Interests.

We may process your personal information where we or a third party have a legitimate interest in processing your personal information. Specifically, we have a legitimate interest in using your personal information for product and service operation, development and internal analytics purposes, and otherwise to improve the safety, security, and performance of our Services. We only rely on our or a third party’s legitimate interests to process your personal information when these interests are not overridden by your rights and interests.

How We Share the Information We Collect
---------------------------------------

This section talks about how we disclose information from or about you that is actually collected.

Vendors and Service Providers.

We may disclose any information we receive or collect with vendors and service providers retained in connection with the provision, operation or improvement of our Services. For example, we may store some of your information in cloud-based storage services.

AI Service Providers.

We may disclose some of your information with artificial intelligence services in order to provide certain features or functionality of the Services. Data sent to third-party AI providers for transcription and summarization is not used for training and is deleted after 30 days.

Analytics Partners.

We use analytics services such as Amplitude, Sentry, Fathom and Segment to collect, process, generate and provide certain analytics data. These third-party services may be provided with some of your information in order to conduct, generate and provide such analytics to or for Limitless and such services may also collect information about your use of other websites, apps, and online resources. To help us understand how you use our Services and to help us improve them, we automatically receive information about your interactions with our Services, like the pages you view, purchases you make, and the dates and times of your visits.

Advertising Partners.

We work with third-party advertising partners to collect and process which pages you visit on our marketing website in order to show you ads that we think may interest you. Some of our advertising partners are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (https://optout.networkadvertising.org) or the Digital Advertising Alliance (https://optout.aboutads.info) and serve ads through cookie-based technologies. Please visit their opt-out pages to learn about how you may opt out of receiving certain web-based personalized ads from member companies. These opt-outs will apply only to our third-party advertising partners that are members of these organizations. These opt-outs will not apply when our partners serve ads through non-cookie based technologies. You can access any settings offered by your mobile operating system to limit ad tracking, or you can install the AppChoices mobile app to learn more about how you may opt out of personalized ads in mobile apps.

As Required By Law and Similar Disclosures.

We may access, preserve, and disclose your information if we believe doing so is required or appropriate to: (a) comply with law enforcement requests and legal process, such as a court order or subpoena; (b) respond to your requests; or (c) protect your, our, or others’ rights, property, or safety.

Merger, Sale, or Other Asset Transfers.

We may transfer your information to service providers, advisors, potential transactional partners, or other third parties in connection with the consideration, negotiation, or completion of a corporate transaction in which we are acquired by or merged with another company, or we sell, liquidate, or transfer all or a portion of our assets. The use of your information following any of these events will be governed by the provisions of this Privacy Policy in effect at the time the applicable information was collected.

Consent.

We may also disclose your information with your permission.

We do not disclose the information we collect from or about you except as described in this Privacy Policy or otherwise disclosed to you at the time of the collection.

Your Choices
------------

Controls.

Any User of the App or Pendant can stop or pause recording at any time, and can delete recordings at any time using the App. Any User of the App can designate which third party apps are integrated, such as Google Calendar.

‍Your European Privacy Rights.

If you are located in the EEA or the UK, you have additional rights described below.

You may request access to the personal information we maintain about you, update and correct inaccuracies in your personal information, restrict or object to the processing of your personal information, have your personal information anonymized or deleted, as appropriate, or exercise your right to data portability to easily transfer your personal information to another company. In addition, you have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, including in your country of residence, place of work or where an incident took place.

You may withdraw any consent you previously provided to us regarding the processing of your personal information at any time and free of charge. We will apply your preferences going forward and this will not affect the lawfulness of the processing before you withdrew your consent.

You may exercise these rights by contacting us using the contact details at the end of this Privacy Policy. Before fulfilling your request, we may ask you to provide reasonable information to verify your identity. Please note that there are exceptions and limitations to each of these rights, and that while any changes you make will be reflected in active user databases promptly or within a reasonable period of time, we may retain personal information for backups, archiving, prevention of fraud and abuse, analytics, satisfaction of legal obligations, or where we otherwise reasonably believe that we have a legitimate reason to do so.

Do Not Track.

There is no accepted standard on how to respond to Do Not Track signals, and we do not respond to such signals.

If you choose not to provide us with the information we collect, some features and functionality of our Services may not work as intended.

Third Parties
-------------

Our Services may contain links to other websites, products, applications or services that we do not own or operate. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these third parties. Please be aware that this Privacy Policy does not apply to your activities on these third-party services or any information you disclose to, or information that is collected by, these third parties. We encourage you to read their privacy policies before providing any information to them or using their products or services.

Security
--------

We use reasonable safeguards and precautions to safeguard the personal information we collect from you, including by employing both physical and electronic measures designed to enhance the security of such information. However, it’s important to note that no method of electronic transmission or storage is entirely foolproof. While we strive to protect your information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security or privacy.

Retention
---------

We take measures to delete your personal information or keep it in a form that does not permit identifying you when this information is no longer necessary or being used for the purposes for which we process it, unless we are required by law to keep this information for a longer period. When we process personal information for our own purposes, we determine the retention period taking into account various criteria, such as the type of services provided to you, the nature and length of our relationship with you, possible re-enrollment with our Services, the impact on our Services we provide to you if we delete some information from or about you, and mandatory retention periods provided by law and the statute of limitations.

California residents have specific privacy rights
-------------------------------------------------

If you are a resident of California, you are granted specific rights regarding access to your personal information.

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the “Shine The Light” law, permits our users who are California residents to request and obtain from us, once a year and free of charge, information about categories of personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared personal information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to us using the contact information provided below.

If you are under 18 years of age, reside in California, and have a registered account with a Service, you have the right to request removal of unwanted data that you publicly post on the Services. To request removal of such data, please contact us using the contact information provided below, and include the email address associated with your account and a statement that you reside in California. We will make sure the data is not publicly displayed on the Services, but please be aware that the data may not be completely or comprehensively removed from all our systems (e.g. backups, etc.).

Children’s Privacy
------------------

Our Services are not intended for children under 18.

We do not knowingly collect, maintain, or use personal information from children under 18 years of age, and no part of our Services is directed to children. If you learn that a child has provided us with personal information in violation of this Privacy Policy, then you may alert us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.limitless.ai/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

International Visitors
----------------------

We store the information we collect from or about you in the United States and may transfer it outside your country. When doing so, we put in place relevant safeguards to afford adequate protection for your personal information.

Our Services are hosted in the United States and intended for visitors located within the United States. If you choose to use the Services from the EEA, the UK, or other regions of the world with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, then please note that you are transferring your personal information outside of those regions to the United States for storage and processing. We may transfer personal information from the EEA or the UK to the U.S. and other third countries based on European Commission-approved or UK Government-approved Standard Contractual Clauses, or otherwise in accordance with applicable data protection laws. Also, we may transfer your data from the U.S. to other countries or regions in connection with storage and processing of data, fulfilling your requests, utilizing third party analytics services, and operating the Services. By providing any information, including personal information, on or to the Services, you consent to such transfer, storage, and processing.

Changes to this Privacy Policy
------------------------------

Changes to this Privacy Policy apply to your use of our Services after the “last updated” date at the top of this Privacy Policy.

We will post any adjustments to the Privacy Policy on this page, and the revised version will be effective when it is posted. If we materially change the ways in which we use or share personal information previously collected from you through the Services, we will notify you through the Services, by email, or by other communication.

Contact Information
-------------------

You may contact us about this Privacy Policy.

Limitless is responsible for processing your information. If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about our processing activities, please email us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.limitless.ai/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).
